# **Darren Lionardo**

Tangerang Selatan, 15834 | 08567777681

darrenlionardo@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/darren-lionardo-935913229/

An informatics student from Universitas Multimedia Nusantara with 1+ years of experience in **web** development and half a year of experience in **mobile app** development. My expertise is comparably better in the **front-end** side than in the back-end side, but full stack is still an option. I'm also very fond of the **ReactJS** framework.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor's Degree - Informatics**

Aug 2020 - May 2024 (Expected)

Universitas Multimedia Nusantara, Tangerang Selatan

- Current GPA: 3.94
- 3x Academic performance scholarship (second, third, and fifth term)
- Intro to Internet Technology Laboratory Assistant (fourth and sixth term)
- Mobile Application Programming Laboratory Assistant (sixth term)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Fullstack Web Developer**

Feb 2023 - Present

Internship, LPPM UMN

- Collect data needs of users
- Perform Code and Execute Requirements for software from the Business Team
- Creating integration of existing modules into the system
- Module database integration to the main database
- Doing Optimize Existing Code
- Eliminate bugs and errors in development
- Communication with the team for delivery updates
- Conduct discussions with end users for the development of information systems
- Perform software response testing on new datasets
- Conduct software reviews with users for feedback

#### **Front-end Web Developer**

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022

External Project, Puskesmas Kelapa Dua

- Responsible for the UI/UX design
- Responsible for all front-end related work
- Helped 25% of the back-end related work
- Laravel was used for development

#### **SKILLS**

**Expert in:** HTML, CSS, SCSS, Tailwind, Javascript, Typescript, PHP, Java, Dart, ReactJS, Laravel, InertiaJS, StorybookJS, Ionic, MySQL, NoSQL (MongoDB), Firebase, Flutter, REST API, GitHub, Git

Intermediate in: Python, C, C#, Code Igniter, Android Studio, Unity, NodeJS, ExpressJS

#### **HONORS & AWARDS**

#### Intro to Internet Technology Laboratory Assistant

Feb 2023 – Present

Lab FTI, Universitas Multimedia Nusantara

- Lectured 2 Intro to Internet Technology lab classes
- Mainly focused on HTML, CSS, JS, and ReactJS
- Responsible for assessing students' assignments and tests

# Mobile Application Programming Laboratory Assistant Feb 2023 – Present

Lab FTI, Universitas Multimedia Nusantara

- Lectured 1 Mobile Application Programming lab classes
- Mainly focused on Android Studio and Kotlin
- Responsible for assessing students' assignments and tests

## Intro to Internet Technology Laboratory Assistant

Feb 2022 – June 2022

Lab FTI, Universitas Multimedia Nusantara

- Lectured 2 Intro to Internet Technology lab classes
- Mainly focused on HTML, CSS, JS, and ReactJS
- Responsible for assessing students' assignments and tests

#### **VOLUNTEER**

### **Research & Development Committee**

Jan 2023 - Present

HMIF, UMN

- Responsible for researching event needs and trend
- Responsible for developing and maintaining hmif.umn.ac.id
- Responsible for developing informatics students soft and hard skills

#### **Website Coordinator**

Jan 2023 - Present

PPIF. UMN

Responsible for developing and maintaining the PPIF website

#### **Public Relation Coordinator**

Jan 2023 - Feb 2023

GGJ, Game Development Club UMN

- Responsible for handling media partners
- Responsible for publication content and planning
- Maintained relations with 4 media partners

#### **Public Relation Coordinator**

Jul 2022 - Nov 2022

G2X, Game Development Club UMN

- Responsible for handling media partners & sponsors
- Responsible for publication content and planning
- Responsible for handling speakers & judges
- Lead four of my PR subordinates
- Maintained relations with 6 media partners and 2 sponsors

#### Global Game Jam Site Organizer

Jan 2022 - Feb 2022

Game Development Club, UMN

• Responsible for managing the Tangerang Global Gam Jam Site

## **Steering Committee**

Jul 2021 - Mar 2022

Game Development Club, UMN

- Helping my coordinator make all of the necessary work plans
- Being an MC for one of the events
- In charge of content publications

### **Global Game Jam Participant**

Jan 2021 - Feb 2021

Game Development Club, UMN

• Successfully made a game in 2 x 24 hours (in a team)

#### **Equipment Committee**

Sep 2020 - Dec 2020

## BIOS, UMN

- Help and manage the official BIOS discord server
- Right hand man for the official zoom meeting

# **English Debate PIC**

Aug 2019 - Sep 2019

INFLAMA, IPEKA SUNTER II

• In charge of guiding and providing the necessary needs in full English to the team.